Mss.B.H262, H 262.p
American Philosophical Society
- Papers
  - Decompression Sickness. Mimeographed Reports, Nos. 127-469
  - Diplocladon
    Kellogg, Remington; Haneda, Yata; Barber, H. S.; Yasaki, Yoshio; Bintwistle, L.; Tuthill, Leonard D.; Witsell, Edward F.
  - Echinodermata Ophiuriods
  - Element Phosphorus
  - Evolution of bioluminiscence and its relation to cell respiration.
  - Final: Decompression Sickness # 1
  - Final: Decompression Sickness # 2
  - Final: Decompression Sickness # 3
  - Final: Decompression Sickness # 4
    Fulton, John F.; Vehue, Alberta L.
  - Final: Decompression Sickness # 5
    Ferris, Eugene B.; Fulton, John B.; Yarbrough, O. D.
  - Final: Decompression Sickness # 6
  - Final: Decompression Sickness # 7
  - Final: Decompression Sickness # 8
    Whiteley, Arthur; Dean, Robert B.
  - Fire-fly...bioluminesscence.
  - Fire-fly Materials # 1
    Buck, John B.
  - Fire-fly Materials # 2
  - Fire-fly Names # 1
    Mote, F. W.; Raghavan, V.
  - Fire-fly Names # 2
    Szent-Gyorgyi, M.; Elderkin, George W.
  - Fire-fly References # 1
    Woodworth, Dorothy; Cornman, Ivan; Warbasse, James P.
  - Fire-fly References # 2
    Lawrence, John H.; Kinkead, Eugene.
  - Fish Bioluminescence Materials # 1
    Giese, Arthur C.; McElroy, William D.; Osgood, Cornelius; Haneda, Yata; Bond, Bar Dee; Springer, Victor G.; Gudger, E. W.
  - Fish Bioluminescence Materials # 2
    Haneda, Yata; Millot, J.
  - Fish Physiology Paper # 1
    Academy Press, Inc.
  - Fish Physiology Paper # 2
    Brown, Margaret E.; Academy Press, Inc.
  - Fish Physiology Paper # 3
    Pickford, Grace E.; Brown, Margaret.
  - Fluorescent Paints
  - General survey of Bioluminiscence
  - Gesner, Doctor Conrad
  - Grignard compounds
  - Ground Strafing - Material removed from Pamphlets # 3
    RE: Ground Strafing
  - Haneda, Yata - Luminous Organisms of Japan and the Far East # 1
  - Haneda, Yata - Luminous Organisms of Japan and the Far East # 2
  - Haneda, Yata - Luminous Organisms of Japan and the Far East # 3
  - Hastings, J. W. - A Personal Diurnal Rhythm of Luminiscence in Gonyaulax Polyedra
  - High Speed Movies of Bubble Flow Past Rod # 1
  - High Speed Movies of Bubble Flow Past Rod # 2
  - Historical Quotes of Phosphares and Fluores
    Cohen, I. Bernard
  - Holborn, Mrs. H[ajo] - Translations
    See also: Miscellaneous extracts on inorganic phosphors, in:
  - Hypothetical Stucture of Luciferin
    Bronk, Detlev W.
  - Jacobaeus, Oliger, Materials.
  - Japanese Research Activities on Bioluminiscence - (Interim Report), Nov. 1949
  - Japanese Research Activities on Bioluminiscence - Report No. 2, April 1950
  - Johnson, Frank [H.]
    Bronk, Detlev W.; American Philosophical Society.
  - Kinetics of Bioluminescent Flashes
  - Kircher, Athanasius, materials # 1
  - Kircher, Athanasius, materials # 2
  - Lectures on Dubois
  - Light in Phosphorus and Flurorescence
    Pasteur Vallery-Radot; Cook, Mel T.; Lutz, Frank E.; Dexter, John S.; Bruner, S. C.; Chapman, Frank M [ichler] (1864-1945); Grey, Robert M.
  - Living Light.
  - Living Light [Advertisement]
  - Living light, talk, 1945
  - Loomis, Alfred Lee (memoir)
    Fortune Magazine
  - Luminescence of Animals
    Fox, H. Munro; Ewen, R. F.; Chambers, Teddy.
  - Luminescence Progress Reports # 1
  - Luminescence Progress Reports # 2
  - Luminescence Progress Reports # 3
  - Luminescence Progress Reports # 4
  - Luminescences (Various) # 1
    Coleman-Norton, P. R.; Haneda, Y.; Hitti, P. K.; Wroth, Larence C.; Carson Rachel L.; Bentley, G. E.; Boyd, Julian P.; Winsatt, William A.; Weitzmann, K.; Wescott, Glenway; Thorington, J Monroe; Shih, Hu; Riggs, Arthur Stanley; Powell, John H.; Monroe, John A.; Duprat, Gabrielle; Jones, Frances Follin
  - Luminescences (Various) # 2
    Cawley, Robert; Harding, Walter; Green, James W.; Buck, John; Warner, Langdon; Yang, Lien-sheng; Johnson, R. P.
  - Luminescent Fungi # 1
    TAF Research Corporation; Johnson, Frank H.; Robbins, WIlliam Jacob; Hastings, J. Woodland; Macrae, Ruth; Rogers, D. P.; Diehl, Willaim W.
  - Luminescent Fungi # 2
    Overbeek, J van; Baker, R. E. D.; Bose, S. R.; Dahlgren, Ulric; Atkinson, George, W.; MacDermott, F. Alexander; Diehl, William W.; Dodge, B. O.
  - Luminescent Fungi # 3
    Buller, A. H. Reginald; Kota, Veeriah; Bergthold, J. W.; Macrae, Ruth; Wassink, E. C.; Abrahamson, Edwin W.; Overbeek, J. van.
  - Luminous Animals
  - Luminous Phenomena. Schistostega, Cats...
    Osterhout, W. J. V.; Lemcke, W. L.; Dahlgren, Ulric; Abbott, Lynn D., Jr.; Noble, G. K.; Lower, George G.; Gudger, E. W.; Moore, Helen; Nance, Mrs. Dorothy; Greb, John W.
  - Marine Biological Laboratory # 1
    Butler, E. G.; Packard, Charles; Allee, W. C.; Riggs, Lawrason; Rudd, H. W. Dwight; Goodrich, H. B.
  - Marine Biological Laboratory # 2
    Armstrong, Philip B.; Packard, Charles.
  - Marine Biological Laboratory # 3
    Sears, Mary; Brown, F. A., Jr.; Weatherby, J. H.
  - Marine Biological Laboratory # 4
    Glaser, Otto C.; Packard, Charles; Brown, Dugald
  - Marine Biological Laboratory # 5
    Packard, Charles; Riggs, Lawrason; Parpart, A. K.; Burdick, C. Lalor; Duryee, William R.; Knowland, William F.; Hussey, G. F., Jr.
  - Marine Biological Laboratory # 6
    Brooks, Matilda M.; Packard, Charles; Riggs, Lawrason; Brodie, Donald M.; Brown, Frank A., Jr.; Mazia, Daniel; Ball, Eric G.; Heilbrunn, L. V.; Redfield, Alfred C[larence] (1890-).; Armstrong, Philip B.; Sterrett, W. E.
  - Marine Biological Laboratory # 7
    Sterrett, W. E.; Duryee, William R.; Ball, Eric; Chambers, Robert; Packard, Charles; Swope, Gerard, Jr.; Armstrong, Philip B.; Jacobs, Merkel H.
  - Marine Biological Laboratory # 8
    Weatherby, J. H.; Packard, Charles; Spencer, R. R.
  - Marine Biological Laboratory # 9
    Riggs, Lawrason; Packard, Charles; Magnuson, Senator; Armstrong, Philip B.; Claff, C. Lloyd.
  - Marine Biological Laboratory # 10
  - Marine Biological Laboratory # 11
    Riggs, Lawrason; Packard, Charles.
  - Marine Biological Laboratory # 12
  - Master Book of Records # 1, 1945-1946
  - Master Book of Records # 2, 1945-1946
  - Master Book of Records # 3, 1945-1946
  - Master Book of Records # 4, 1945-1946
  - Master Book of Records # 5, 1945-1946
  - Mechanism of light production in animals.
  - Mechanism of wounding by high velocity missles # 1
    Turner, Kenneth B.; Forbes, T. R.; Fulton, John F.
  - Mechanism of wounding by high velocity missles # 2
  - Mechanism of wounding by high velocity missles # 3
  - Mechanism of wounding by high velocity missles # 4
  - Mechanism of wounding by high velocity missles # 5
  - Mechanism of wounding by high velocity missles # 6
  - Miscellaneous Extracts on Inorganic Phosphars
    Holborn, Mrs. Hajo; Caruthers, Ralph H.
  - Miscellaneous Materials, Chiefly on Luminescence # 1
  - Miscellaneous Materials, Chiefly on Luminescence # 2
  - Miscellaneous Microsecond Photographs # 1
  - Miscellaneous Microsecond Photographs # 2
  - Miscellaneous Microsecond Photographs # 3
  - Miscellaneous Microsecond Photographs # 4
  - Miscellaneous Microsecond X-Rays # 1
  - Miscellaneous Microsecond X-Rays # 2
    Sloane, John E.; Crawford, E. M.; Slack, Charles M.; Turner, Kenneth B.
  - Miscellaneous Microsecond X-Rays # 3
  - Miscellaneous Microsecond X-Rays # 4
  - Miscellaneous Microsecond X-Rays # 5
  - Miscellaneous Microsecond X-Rays # 6
  - Miscellaneous Notes on Luminiscence # 1
  - Miscellaneous Notes on Luminiscence # 2
  - Missle Casualties Report, Nos. 1-2
  - Missle Casualties Report, Nos. 3-5
  - Missle Casualties Report, No. 6, Part 1
  - Missle Casualties Report, No. 6, Part 2
  - Missle Casualties Report, No. 6, Part 3
  - Missle Casualties Report, No. 6, Part 4
  - Missle Casualties Report, Nos. 6-7
  - Missle Casualties Report, Nos. 8-11
  - Missle Casualties Report, Nos. 9-12
  - Missle Casualties Report, Nos. 15-17
  - Missle casualties reports. (Mimeographed) No. 2
  - Missle casualties reports. (Mimeographed) No. 6
  - Missle casualties reports. (Mimeographed) Nos. 9-10
  - Missle casualties reports. (Mimeographed) Nos. 11-14
  - Mitogenetic rays.
    Williams, E. F.
  - Mollusks
    Turner, Ruth D.; Bartsch, Paul.
  - Noctiluca - Original Notes # 1
  - Noctiluca - Original Notes # 2
  - Notes on Luminescence - Miscellany # 1
    Strehler, B. L.
  - Notes on Luminescence - Miscellany # 2
  - Notes on Luminescence - Miscellany # 3
    Moore, J. Percy
  - Notes on Luminescence - Miscellany # 4
    Sohn, I. G.
  - Notes on luminous barometer
  - Occasional Papers # 1
    535.35: H 26, no. 106
  - Occasional Papers # 2
  - Ohryxothrix
  - Okochi, Nobusada, and S. Sakai. Studies on the nutrition of luminous bacteria, 1947
  - Pacific Oceanic Biology., 1946
  - Pacific Oceanic Biology., 1947
  - Phengodes.
  - Photodynamic action.
  - Physiology of crustacea # 1
    Waterman, Talbot H.; Academic Press, Inc.; Adams, Elizabeth E.; Seham, D.; Jacoby, Kurt.
  - Physiology of crustacea # 2
  - Physiology of crustacea # 3
  - Physiology of crustacea # 4
  - Physiology of crustacea # 5
  - Physiology of crustacea # 6
  - Pisces. [Bioluminescence]
  - Poetry on fire-fly and glow-worm.
    Wescott, Glenway.
  - Quotations from Authors in re fire-flies # 1
  - Quotations from Authors in re fire-flies # 2
  - Quotations from Authors in re fire-flies # 3
  - Railroad worm
  - Rays from organisms
    Colli, Laura; Facchini, U.; Strehler, Bernard L.; Reynolds, George T.
  - Report on Bubble Formation No. 77
    Stanton, Madeline; Fulton, John F.; DuBois, Eugene F.
  - Report on Bubble Formation No. 105
    DuBois, Eugene
  - Report on Bubble Formation No. 106
  - Report on Bubble Formation (Between No. 106 and No. 229. Not Sent)
  - Report on Bubble Formation No. 229 (Part 1)
  - Report on Bubble Formation No. 229 (Part 2)
  - Report on Bubble Formation No. 229 (Part 3)
    Whittingham, H. E.; Fulton, John F.; Wigodsky, Herman S.; Flexner, Louis; Andrus, E. Cowles; DuBois, Eugene P.; Richards, A. N.
  - Reports # 1
    Schauer, Charles H.
  - Reports # 2
  - Reports # 3
  - Reports # 4
  - Reports # 5
  - Reports # 6
  - Rivinus and Boehme, De Noctu Lucentibus
    Schullian, Dorothy M.
  - Sachs, P. J. [Philip Jacob], (1627-1672)
  - Shrimp
    Kemp, Stanley; Schmitt, Waldo L.; Dahlgren, Ulric; Keeley, F. J.; Welsh, William W.; Moore, H. F.; Russell, F. S.
  - Shrimp Materials # 1
    Tattersall, W. M.; Schmitt, Waldo L.; Chace, Fenner, A., Jr.
  - Shrimp Materials # 2
    Schmitt, Waldo L.; Wilson, Charles B.; Chace, Fenner A.; Shoemaker, Clarence R.; Burkenroad, M. D.
  - Siloxene # 1
    Andrews, W. S.; Dahlgren, Ulric.
  - Siloxene # 2
    Oliver, James A.; Tee-Van, John; Downs, Wilbur G.; Kenny, Julian S.; Parker, H. W.
  - Siloxene # 3
  - Source Material # 1
  - Source Material # 2
  - Squids # 1
    Nishiziki, Ichiro; Chamberlin, R. V.; Schmitt, Waldo L.; Hastings, J. W.
  - Squids # 2
    Hastings, J. Woodland; Sweeney, Beatrice M.
  - Students on Fire-Flies # 1
  - Students on Fire-Flies # 2
    Alexander, Robert S.; Hix, John.
  - Students on Fire-Flies # 3
  - Studies on Wound Ballistics. Princeton University # 1
  - Studies on Wound Ballistics. Princeton University # 2
    Atlantic Monthly Press; Bush, Vannevar; Day, Tuckerman; Callender, George R.; French, Ralph W.; Lockwood, John S.
  - Total Luminous Efficiency of Luminous Bacteria
    Cady, Francis E.
  - Translations: Electrolum and Ignis Lambens: Aurora Borealis
    Hundley, James M.; Chinard, Gilbert.
  - Translations on Luminescence
  - Underwater Ballistics Album # 1
  - Underwater Ballistics Album # 2
  - Underwater Ballistics Album # 3
    Birkhoff, Garrett; McMillen, J. Howard; Hooper, Lynn J.; Forbes, T. R.
  - U.S. Bureau of Standards publications on luminescence.
  - Various Original Writings on Fire Fly and Glow Worms # 1
    Marquand, Eleanor C.; Egbert, Virginia; Panofsky, Erwin.
  - Various Original Writings on Fire Fly and Glow Worms # 2
  - Various Original Writings on Fire Fly and Glow Worms # 3
  - Various Original Writings on Fire Fly and Glow Worms # 4
  - Wound Ballistics - Final Report # 1
    French, Ralph W.; Callender, George R.; Richards, A. N.
  - Wound Ballistics - Final Report # 2
  - Wound Ballistics - Final Report # 3
  - Wound Ballistics - Final Report # 4
  - Wound Ballistics - Final Report # 5
  - Wound Ballistics - Final Report # 6
  - Wound Ballistics - Final Report # 7
  - Wound Ballistics - Final Report # 8
    Gruber, C. G.; Odell, Floyd A.
  - Wound Ballistics - Final Report # 9
  - Wound Ballistics - Final Report # 10
  - Wound Ballistics - Final Report # 11
  - Wound Ballistics - Final Report # 12
  - Wound Ballistics - Final Report # 13
  - Wound Ballistics - Final Report # 14
  - Wound Ballistics Statements # 1
    Smith, Nichol H.; Marble, John Putnam
  - Wound Ballistics Statements # 2
    Fulton, J. F.
  - Wound Ballistics Statements # 3
  - Wound Ballistics Statements # 4
    Fulton, John F.; Southworth, Hamilton; MacDougall, D. P.
  - Wound Ballistics Typewritten Reports # 1
    Fulton, John F.; Weed, Lewis H.; Redfield, Alfred [Clarence] (1890-); Irving, Larry; Wilson, E. Bright, Jr.
  - Wound Ballistics Typewritten Reports # 2
    Redfield, Alfred.
  - Wound Ballistics Typewritten Reports # 3
  - Wound Ballistics Typewritten Reports # 4
  - Wound Ballistics Typewritten Reports # 5
  - Wound Ballistics Typewritten Reports # 6